Finding aid for University Herbarium (University of Michigan) Records, 1744-1745, 1851-1981, and 2001-2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Bartlett, Harley Harris, 1744-1855; 1875-1959
  - Correspondence and Associated Materials, 1875-1959
    - C
      - Cocks, R.S., 1909 (Box 6)
        (col. Rhus; Dioscorea)
      - Cohen, Isadore, 1946 (Box 6)
      - Coker, R.E. (Box 6)
        (see N.R.C. Fellowships)
      - Cole, Catherine A., 1946-1949 (Box 6)
      - Cole, Emma (Box 6)
        (see Stearns, Frances L.)
      - Cole, Fay Cooper, 1921; 1957 (Box 6)
        (Philippines; Indonesia)
      - Cole, L.J., 1928 (Box 6)
        (appt. to Am. Soc. Nat. council, invitation to speak-Wisconsin)
      - Colegrove, Kenneth I.. (Box 6)
        (see U.S. Office of Strategic Services)
      - Collier, A., 1957 (Box 6)
        (nomenclature)
      - Collier, John, 1950 (Box 6)
        (Inst. of Ethnic Affairs)
      - Colligan, Francis J. (Box 6)
        (see U.S. Dept. of State & U.S. Dept. of State-Fulbright Funds)
      - Collins, Frank S., 1908-1915 (Box 6)
        (algae; re position in Wash.)
      - Collins, J. Franklin, 1908-1909 (Box 6)
        (mosses)
      - Colonial Office, Eng, 1956 (Box 6)
      - Committees, 1917-1952
        - National Research Council Committee on Philippines, 1947 (Box 6)
        - U.S. Botanical Gardens Planning Committee, 1934 (Box 6)
        - U.S. Nat. Herb., Bot. Soc. Am., 1945-1947 (Box 6)
          (other references)
        - U of M Committee of Advisers in L.S.A. & Forestry, 1933 (Box 6)
        - U of M Committee on Biol. Station, 1947-1949 (Box 6)
        - U of M Committee on Deanship, 1944; 1950-1952 (Box 6)
        - U of M Committee Div. Biol. Sci., 1947-1951 (Box 6)
        - U of M Committee on Rhodes Scholarships, 1932-1935 (Box 6)
        - U of M Committee on Univ. Lands, 1932-1946 (Box 6)
        - U of M Executive Comm., L.S.A., 1945; 1947 (Box 6)
        - U of M George Reserve, 1948 (Box 6)
        - U of M Library Committee, 1925-1946 (Box 6)
        - U of M Mud Lake Area, 1946 (Box 6)
        - U of M-Phoenix, 1948-1951 (Box 6)
        - U of M Research Comm., 1917 (Box 6)
      - Commonwealth Ins. Co., 1930-1939 (Box 6)
      - Conferences, 1932-1949
        - Biological Conf., Mich. Schoolmasters' Club 12 items, 1932-1933 (Box 6)
        - Conference on Student Training in Research Projects, U of M 3 items, 1949 (Box 6)
      - Conger, Beach, earthquake calendar painting (Box 6)
      - Conger, Paul S., 1945-1948 (Box 6)
        (A.F. collecting-diatoms)
      - Congresses, 1926-1956
        - Eighth Amer. Sci. Congress, 1940 (Box 6)
        - Anthropological Congress, 1955-1956 (Box 6)
        - Tenth Chilean Gen. Sci. Congress, 1944 (Box 6)
        - Sixth Int. Bot. Congress, Amsterdam, 1933 (Box 6)
        - Seventh Int. Hot. Congress, Stockholm, 1950 (Box 6)
        - Sixth Int. Congress Genetics, Ithaca, N.Y., 1932 (Box 6)
        - Twelfth Int. Hort. Congress, 1938 (Box 6)
        - Java Congress, 1929 (Box 6)
        - Third Pan-Pacific Sci. Congress, Tokyo, 1926 (Box 6)
          (1 item & group photograph)
        - Fifth Pac. Sci. Congress, Ottawa, 1933 (Box 6)
        - Sixth Pac. Sci. Congress, Berkeley, Calif., 1939 (Box 6)
        - Seventh Pac. Sci. Congress, New Zea, 1949 (Box 6)
        - Eighth Pac. Sci. Congress, Manila, 1953 (Box 6)
        - Ninth Pac. Sci. Congress, Bangkok, 1937 (Box 6)
        - Third S.A. Bot. Congress, Lima, 1956 (Box 6)
      - Conifer Society of America, 1932 (Box 6)
        (formation of Society)
      - Conklin, Harold C., 1947-1958 (Box 6)
        (Philippines, see also Linguistics)
      - Conklin, Robert J., 1947 (Box 6)
        (fac. U. Philippines)
      - Connable, Alfred B., 1945 (Box 6)
        (Museum situation at Michigan)
      - Conover, J. Towne, 1948-1950 (Box 6)
        (student; see also Herbarium-Collections, J.T.C.)
      - Constance, Clifford, 1945 (Box 6)
        (re R. H. Pearson)
      - Constantine, Josefina, Philippines (Box 6)
      - Conzatti, Cassiano, Mexico (Box 6)
        (see also Rockefeller Foundation; White, Stephen S.)
      - Cook, David R., 1945 (Box 6)
      - Cook, Orator F., 1939; 1955 (Box 6)
      - Cook, Robert C., 1957 (Box 6)
        (biography)
      - Cook, S.F. (Box 6)
      - Cooley, C.E. (Box 6)
        (see USDA-Entomol., Pl. Quar.)
      - Cooley, Mary E., 1948 (Box 6)
        (Wilkes exped.)
      - Cooley, Mortimer E., 1939 (Box 6)
      - Coolidge, Harold J., 1936-1957 (Box 6)
        (Nat. Res. Council-Pacific)
      - Cooper, Bernarr, 1945 (Box 6)
        (see War-related-CATS)
      - Cooper, G. Proctor III (Box 6)
        (see Guggenheim Foundation)
      - Cooprider, J.L., 1955 (Box 6)
      - Copeland, Edwin B., 1928-1953 (Box 6)
        (ferns; M.S.Clemens; see also Herbarium Collections-Univ. of Calif.)
      - Copeland, R.A., 1944-1945 (Box 6)
      - Copeland, R.S. (Box 6)
        (see U.S. Senate)
      - Copley, Frank O., 1946 (Box 6)
        (interdisciplinary major)
      - Copley Prints (Box 6)
      - Core, Earl L., 1953 (Box 6)
        (A.G.B.-Nuttall)
      - Corlett, W.S., 1945 (Box 6)
      - Cornelis, Rita, 1936 (Box 6)
      - Correll, Donovan S. 1937, 1939. 1950 re position; Strophanthus, 1937-1950 (Box 6)
      - Cortright, Richard, 1948 (Box 6)
      - Cotner, Frank B., 1929; 1948 (Box 6)
        (coal)
      - Cotter, Shirley, 1948 (Box 6)
      - Coulter, John M., 1919 (Box 6)
      - Courcelles, M.J., 1957 (Box 6)
      - Covas, Guillermo, 1948 (Box 6)
      - Cowan, Richard S., 1946-, re position (Box 7)
      - Cowan, W.A., 1958 (Box 7)
      - Cowden, Roy, 1927-1943 (Box 7)
        (personal, 8 items)
      - Cowdry, N.H., 1924 (Box 7)
        (plants from China)
      - Cowles, Henry C., 1927-1934 (Box 7)
        (also National Research Council-Fellowships)
      - Cox, Creed F. (Box 7)
        (see Philippines-University; Bartlett-Santos Exch.)
      - Cox, J.A. (Box 7)
        (see Oak Ridge National Laboratory)
      - Craig, Hardin, 1947 (Box 7)
        (fac.-U. Philippines)
      - Cram, Robert V., 1909-1945 (Box 7)
        (personal; Harvard, Juniata, University of Minnesota)
      - Crane, R.I., 1947 (Box 7)
      - Cratty, R.I., 1910 (Box 7)
      - Crayton, F.M., Rhus (Box 7)
      - Creighton, Harriet, 1951 (Box 7)
        (see "Bot. Soc. Amer."; A.I.B.S.; Nat. Herb.)
      - Creswell, A., "Early Muslim Architecture" (Box 7)
      - Crist, Raymond E., 1956 (Box 7)
      - Crocker, R.S., 1946 (Box 7)
      - Crocker, Jilliam, 1929-1931 (Box 7)
        (plant physiology)
      - Crofts, F.S., 1920-1945 (Box 7)
        (Harper & Brothers) publication-biographies)
      - Crook, George H., 1945 (Box 7)
      - Crosby, Elizabeth, 1956 (Box 7)
      - Cross, Aureal T., 1944 (Box 7)
        (coal fossils)
      - Cross, George L., 1936 (Box 7)
        (recommendations: Hermann, Mueller, Walker, Clover, Moldenke, Archer, Erlanson)
      - Cross, J.C., 1946 (Box 7)
        (recommendation)
      - Crum, C.W., 1931 (Box 7)
        (local flora)
      - Crum, Howard A., 1949-1952 (Box 7)
      - Cruz, Jos; P., Philippines (Box 7)
      - Cummins, George B., 1927-1929 (Box 7)
      - Cummins, Harold, 1925 (Box 7)
        (China)
      - Curtis, C.H., 1951 (Box 7)
        (exhibit at Kew, order for "My Garden")
      - Curtis, Elsie, 1946 (Box 7)
        (applicant)
      - Curtis, Francis D., 1929-1937 (Box 7)
        (Education-Biology)
      - Curtis, John T., 1955 (Box 7)
        (birches)
      - Curtis, W.A., 1929 (Box 7)
        (Flora of Judith Basin, Mont.)
      - Cuthbert, Alfred, 1917 (Box 7)
        (photograph album)
      - Cutler, Vern H., 1945 (Box 7)
      - Cutshall, Alden, 1958 (Box 7)
    - D
      - Dacca Univ., 1957 (Box 7)
      - DaCosta, Gordan C., 1945 (Box 7)
        (applicant-Grad. Sch.)
      - DaCruz, Daniel, 1921; 1926 (Box 7)
        ("Unfolding of Life")
      - V. Daele, E., 1956 (Box 7)
      - Daguio, Amador T., 1947 (Box 7)
      - Dahl, A. Orville, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Dahlgren, Bror E., 1947 (Box 7)
      - Dake, H.C., 1949 (Box 7)
      - Dale, Ernest E., 1920-1939 (Box 7)
        (race; genetics, etc.)
      - Dana, Samuel T., 1927-1945 (Box 7)
        (inc. Eberwhite Woods see also Gordon, S.; Pavetti-Morin, C. & Eberwhite Woods material)
      - Daniels, Francis, 1910 (Box 7)
      - Danielson, Karl, 1928 (Box 7)
        (student, collector)
      - Dansereau, Pierre, 1951; 1953 (Box 7)
        (see also A.G.B.)
      - Darlington, H.T., 1929-1945 (Box 7)
      - Darlmowski, Alfred P., 1921 (Box 7)
        (support for Russian scientists)
      - Davidson, Mrs. L. Cook, 1956 (Box 7)
      - Davidson, M.E., 1936 (Box 7)
        (plant collection-Panama)
      - Davidson, T., 1910 (Box 7)
        (collector-Rhus)
      - Davis, Alva L., 1949 (Box 7)
      - Davis, Annie E. P., 1926 (Box 7)
        (personal-re Sumatra trip)
      - Davis, Bradley Moore, 1937-1953 (Box 7)
        (photographic file & photograph album)
      - Davis, Charles A., 1908-1914 (Box 7)
        (summer work with Geol. Surv.)
      - Davis, Edgar B. (Box 7)
        (see Rubber Investigation, Sumatra)
      - Davis, Everett P., 1950 (Box 7)
        (antibiotics in higher plants)
      - Davis, L. Irby, 1941 (Box 7)
        (amateur; Verbena; publication)
      - Davis, Roy M., 1945 (Box 7)
      - Davis, T.R.A., 1947 (Box 7)
        (Cook Islands)
      - Davis, d.M., 1911 (Box 7)
        ("Johnson" controversy)
      - Dawkins, H.C., 1955 (Box 7)
        (Fire & Prim. :mgr.)
      - Dawson, E. Yale, 1944 (Box 7)
        (Latin descriptions)
      - Dawson, Glen, 1959-1961 (Box 7)
        ("Japanese Botany...")
      - Dawson, Ray F., 1945 (Box 7)
      - Day, Mary Anna, 1910 (Box 7)
        (Gray Herb.)
      - Dayton, William A.,, U.S. Forest Service, 1945-1952 (Box 7)
      - Deadman, Hazel B., 1925 (Box 7)
        (peat-Pt. Sanilac)
      - Deam, Charles C., 1905-1953 (Box 7)
        (Deam oak; among much else; photographs of C.C.D. & H.H.B. with Deam oak)
      - Deam, Charles C., Material supplied by Roberta (Deam) Ortenburger, Biographical material inc. photographs & clippings (Photographic file) (Box 7)
      - Dean, Donald, 1951-1953 (Box 7)
        (student; see also A.G.B.)
      - de Beausset, Valery, 1955-1956 (Box 7)
        (Formosa; shinhokutolite)
      - de Bracco, Maria, 1945-1948 (Box 7)
        (Lemnaceae)
      - De Crocker, Robert J., 1945 (Box 7)
      - Deevey, Edward S., 1951 (Box 7)
        (radiocarbon dating)
      - Degener, Otto, 1936-1957 (Box 7)
        (Hawaiian collections (Isa Hansen Degener))
      - DeGraff, Philip A., 1953 (Box 7)
        (hart's tongue fern)
      - Deibel, Durus J., 1945 (Box 7)
        (identification)
      - De la Cruz, Eugenio (Box 7)
        (see Uichanco, L.B.)
      - De Leon, Ricardo P., 1948 (Box 7)
      - Demmon, E.L., 1932-1951 (Box 7)
        (timberlands)
      - Denny, F.E., 1929 (Box 7)
        (position)
      - Denyes, Arliss, 1947 (Box 7)
        (recommendation letters)
      - Dept. of Public Instruction-Lansing, 1932 (Box 7)
        (teacher certification)
      - DeSelm, H.R., 1958 (Box 7)
      - Detrick, H.J., 1947 (Box 7)
      - Detroit Convention & Tourist Bureau, 1928 (Box 7)
        (Botanical Gardens)
      - Devereux, George, 1937 (Box 7)
        (ethnology-Indonesian)
      - DeVries, Hugo, 1912-1928 (Box 7)
        (see also Photograph Album)
      - Devroey, E.J., 1955 (Box 7)
      - Dewey, Bradley, 1944 (Box 7)
        (rubber)
      - Dice, Lee R., 1925-1949 (Box 7)
        (see also "Natural Areas")
      - Dickson, F.G. (Box 7)
        (see Burma Survey)
      - Dickinson, Edwin D., 1947 (Box 7)
      - Dickson, B.T., 1928 (Box 7)
        ("Bot. Abstracts")
      - Diels, L. (Box 7)
      - Dieterle, Jenny V.D. (Box 7)
      - Dipasupil, P. (Box 7)
        (see Marasigan, P.)
      - Dirkson, Everett (Box 7)
        (see U.S. House of Representatives)
      - Ditzler, R.E., 1945 (Box 7)
      - Dixon, Henry N., 1923-1931 (Box 7)
        (Sumatran mosses)
      - Dodge, Bernard O., 1925 (Box 7)
        (rusts of Rubus)
      - Dodge, Carroll W., 1945 (Box 7)
      - Dodge, Charles K., 1911 (Box 7)
        (plant collections-Mich.)
      - Dolf, Howard, 1939 (Box 7)
        (advice for beginning botanist)
      - Domantay, Jose S., 1949 (Box 7)
      - Dombras, Theodore T., 1958 (Box 7)
        (recommendations)
      - Dorn, Frank, 1948 (Box 7)
      - Dorr, Harold M., 1945 (Box 7)
        ("regulations of the faculty")
      - Dorsett, Robert, 1948 (Box 7)
      - Doty, Maxwell S., 1958 (Box 7)
      - Douglass, Benjamin W., 1910-1939 (Box 7)
        (Indianapolis friend, and trees see also Photograph Album)
      - Downing, Margaret B., 1915 (Box 7)
        (re E.L.Greene)
      - Drapkin, Herbert, 1945 (Box 7)
      - Drew, William B., 1934-1954 (Box 7)
      - Drews, Robin A., 1945-1954 (Box 7)
        (CATS student to staff, M.S.U., Okinawa; also A.G.B. & Troyer, M.E.)
      - Driesbach, Robert R., 1938 (Box 7)
        (transparent mounts)
      - Droleskey, E.A., 1945 (Box 7)
      - Drouet, Francis, 1946 (Box 7)
        (alga identification)
      - Dugand, Armando, 1941 (Box 7)
        (palms-Bogota)
      - Duggar, Benjamin M., 1929 (Box 7)
      - Dukes, W.C., 1910 (Box 7)
      - Duncan, Donald P., 1945 (Box 7)
      - Dunham, Harmon, 1938-1947 (Box 7)
      - DuPont, H.A., 1925 (Box 7)
        (Aesculus DuPontii)
      - Durrell, Harold C., 1939 (Box 7)
        (genealogy, Roger Williams)
      - Durst, Samuel, 1939 (Box 7)
        (recommendation letter)
      - Dusman, Joseph T., 1945 (Box 7)
        (bracken fern)
      - Dyer, Harold J., 1945 (Box 7)
      - Dyson, J.W. (Box 7)
        (see Li, Ming-Gi)
    - E
      - Eaby, Robert W., 1949 (Box 7)
      - Eames, Arthur J., 1932-1951 (Box 7)
        (Seward's trip, Wildlife Res. Survey)
      - Eames, Edwin H., 1909 (Box 7)
        (plant specimens)
      - Eames, Edwin H., 1909 (Box 7)
      - East Indies Inst., 1941-1946 (Box 7)
        (later Southeast Asia Inst.)
      - Eastwood, Alice, 1938 (Box 7)
      - Ebalo, Liborio E., 1936-1947 (Box 7)
        (collector, see also J.K. Santos)
      - Ebeling, A.W., 1910 (Box 7)
        (reply to request for plants from Mo.)
      - E.C.A.-Joint Committee on Rural Reconstruction, 1951 (Box 7)
        (rural reconstruction in China)
      - Echavez, Pastor S., 1951 (Box 7)
      - Ecological Society of America, 1934 (Box 7)
      - Echols, John M., 1956 (Box 7)
        (linguistics-Indonesia)
      - Eclipse Expedition -- Phoenix Island (Box 7)
      - Edmunds, C.W., 1926-1944 (Box 7)
        (personal; P.R. White)
      - Edmunds, Charles W. "Buddy", 1944 (Box 7)
        (personal; A.F. collecting)
      - Aunt Edna, 1935 (Box 7)
        (personal -- family)
      - Edwards Bros., 1945 (Box 7)
      - Effinger, John R., 1919-1933 (Box 7)
        (Administration -- Botanical Gardens; see also Exped: Carpelan)
      - Eggan, Fred, 1936-1958 (Box 7)
        (Philippines -- anthropology)
      - Egler, Frank E., 1958 (Box 7)
      - Egner, D.W., 1924-1936 (Box 7)
        (Javanese wayanga; Sumatra)
      - Ehlers, John, 1924-1946 (Box 7)
        (administration; Colorado plants)
      - Ehrlich, Wallace J., 1945 (Box 7)
        (A.F. Collecting)
      - Eichstaedt, E.A., 1936 (Box 7)
        (Earhart estate)
      - Eitel, Edmund H., 1921-1922 (Box 7)
        (adonite -- Adonis vernalis)
      - Ekvall, Robert B., 1954 (Box 7)
        (Korea)
      - Eldorado Mining & Refining Co., 1948 (Box 7)
        (O.N.R. -- Port Radium)
      - Elizabeth, personal -- niece? (Box 7)
      - Ellersten, Birger, 1938 (Box 7)
        (re position in Sumatra)
      - Elliott, E.W., 1946-1947 (Box 7)
        (A.F. collecting, hydrophonics)
      - Ellis, Charlotte C., 1910 (Box 7)
      - Ellison, Bernard R., 1946 (Box 7)
        (re teaching)
      - Elmer, Adolph D.E. & Emma, 1924-1950 (Box 7)
        (plant specimens, biographical)
      - Elqueta, Manuel, 1944 (Box 7)
        (Chile -- potato)
      - "Else", personal (Box 7)
      - Embrey, Olivia, 1938-1939 (Box 7)
      - Emerson, Gertrude, 1922 (Box 7)
        ("Asia")
      - Emerson, Ralph, 1937; 1949 (Box 7)
        (re Conover)
      - Emerson, R.A., 1919-1939 (Box 7)
        (corn pigments, etc.)
      - Emerson, Sterling H., 1922-1950 (Box 7)
        (student (photographic file))
      - Encarnaction, Felipa T., 1941 (Box 7)
      - Encyclopedia of Michigan (Box 7)
        (see Fuller, George N.)
      - Enders, Robert K., 1948 (Box 7)
      - Engel, Albert J. (Box 7)
      - Entrican, A.R., 1956 (Box 7)
      - Epling, Carl, 1931-1946 (Box 7)
      - Erdtman, O. Gunnar E., 1938 (Box 7)
        (pollen)
      - Erickson, Ray C., 1959 (Box 7)
        (Plummer's Island)
      - Erlanson, Carl O., 1925-1958 (Box 7)
        (student, see also Liu, Su-Ying)
      - Erlanson, Eileen W. (Box 7)
        (see Macfarlane, E.W.E.)
      - Evans, Alexander W., 1908-1950 (Box 7)
        (bryophytes)
      - Evans, Mr. & Mrs. Clifford, 1955 (Box 8)
      - Evans, George W., 1909 (Box 8)
        (recommendation -- HHB)
      - Evans, Griffith C., 1910-1951 (Box 8)
        (personal -- Harvard, Rome, Rice Institute, University of California Berkeley)
      - Evans, James G., 1947 (Box 8)
        (faculty -- U. Philippines)
      - Evans, Richard T., 1909-1940 (Box 8)
        (personal -- Harvard, Pei-Yang University, Tientsin)
      - Evans, Ruth, 1911-1938 (Box 8)
        (personal -- Wellesley)
      - Evans, S.B., 1955-1956 (Box 8)
      - Eves, Donald, 1945 (Box 8)
      - Ewan, Joseph, 1945-1957 (Box 8)
        (see also USDA -- BPI -- Plant Exploration & Introduction)
      - Expedition, 1930-1949
        - Atomic Bombing-Bikini (Box 8)
          (see Taylor, Wm. Randolph)
        - Carnegie, 1930 (Box 8)
        - Carpelan-East Indies, 1931-1932 (Box 8)
        - Cooper Third Caribbean Bot. Surv., 1932 (Box 8)
        - Darwin Memorial (von Hagen), 1933-1936 (Box 8)
        - L.R. Hubbard, 1932 (Box 8)
          (directions for collecting)
        - Eugene Mosier Expedition to Tibet, 1949 (Box 8)
          (?, 1 letter to A.R.Gage)
        - Niebling-Kelley, 1931 (Box 8)
          (?, Brazil (E.M. Kelley))
        - Papuan-Australian (Box 8)
        - Roerich (Box 8)
          (see also Koelz, Merrill)
        - Seven Seas, 1946 (Box 8)
        - Stuart Springer, Caribbean (Box 8)
        - Kingdon Ward, 1947 (Box 8)
          (Burma)
      - Eyster, B.C., 1939; 1945 (Box 8)
      - Ezri, Marguerite, 1938 (Box 8)
    - F
      - Faculty Research Fund-Monthly Statements, 1927-1940 (Box 8)
      - Fahs, Charles B. (Box 8)
        (see Rockefeller Foundation)
      - Fairbanks, Lulu H., 1916 (Box 8)
        (?, collection-China)
      - Fairchild, David, 1925-1955 (Box 8)
      - Fairchild, Henry Pratt, 1941- (Box 8)
        ("proof")
      - Falconer, J.I., 1947 (Box 8)
      - Fansler, Dean S., 1937 (Box 8)
      - Fansler, Priscilla, 1941 (Box 8)
      - Faquendes, A.B., 1945 (Box 8)
        (re Brazilian students)
      - Farlow, Jilliam G., 1909; 1920 (Box 8)
        (Farlow memorial)
      - Farrall, A.W., 1947 (Box 8)
      - Farwell, Oliver A., 1921-1932 (Box 8)
        (plants; publishing)
      - Fatherless Children of France (Marie Vireux) (Box 8)
      - Feather, Norman J., 1938 (Box 8)
        (appreciation-student)
      - Feliciano, Jose M., 1949 (Box 8)
      - Felizardo, Mamerta, Philippines (Box 8)
      - Fellows, Katherine A. (Box 8)
        (student; see also Library-U of M)
      - Fellows, Perry A., 1952 (Box 8)
        (Ethiopia)
      - Fennell, T.A. SHADA, 1942 (Box 8)
        (Haiti)
      - Ferguson, Homer (Box 8)
      - Fernald, Merritt L., 1906-1945 (Box 8)
        (collections, publication; recommendations; Gray Index, see also "Rhodora", Photograph Album)
      - Fernandes, Bill, 1952 (Box 8)
      - Fernandez, Leandro H., 1936 (Box 8)
        (U. Philippines-fisheries)
      - Ferreyra, Ramon, 1956 (Box 8)
      - Ferris, Roxana, 1940 (Box 8)
        (palms; L.R. Abrams)
      - Field, Geoff, 1943 (Box 8)
        (Buenos Aires, personal)
      - Field, John, 1950-1951 (Box 8)
        (O.N.R.; Aleutians)
      - Finch, G., 1932 (Box 8)
        (see Expedition: Hubbard)
      - Fincham, Donald G., 1936 (Box 8)
      - Fincher, J.A., 1946 (Box 8)
      - Fink, Bruce, 1922 (Box 8)
        (protoplasm)
      - Fink, George & Ann, 1947 (Box 8)
        (Philippines; personal)
      - Fire in Relation to Primitive Agriculture and Grazing in the Tropics: Annotated Bibliography, 1955-1959 (Box 8)
      - Fisch, Max H., 1949 (Box 8)
        (herbals, genealogy, see also USDA-For. Agr. Relations, For. Agr. Service and Special Interest File)
      - Fischer, Arthur F., 1944-1948 (Box 8)
        (Cinchona, Philippines, C.E. Sando)
      - Fish, H.D., 1927-1928 (Box 8)
      - Fishburn, John, 1941-1942 (Box 8)
        (Cinchona, quinine, Philippines)
      - Fisher, C.A., 1947 (Box 8)
        (Philippines education)
      - Fisher, Edgar J., 1944-1945 (Box 8)
        (Inst. International Educ.)
      - Fisher, George A., Jr., 1959 (Box 8)
      - Fitch, Ethel a John T., 1945 (Box 8)
      - Fitzpatrick, Robert F., 1918-1927 (Box 8)
      - Fleming, Robert L., 1945-1956 (Box 8)
        (collecting, Himalayas; ferns; Burma; see also R. Khanwa and R.R. Stewart)
      - Flora Malesiana (Box 8)
        (see Van Steenis, C.E.G.J.)
      - Foa, Garlo, 1962 (Box 8)
        (Strophanthus)
      - Focke, Wilhelm O., 1911 (Box 8)
      - Fogg, John M., 1955 (Box 8)
        (oaks)
      - Foley, Donald D., 1946 (Box 8)
        (collecting)
      - Fontanna, Stanley G., 1955 (Box 8)
        (U of M fac.)
      - Forbush, Lothrop M., 1945 (Box 8)
      - Ford, A.H., 1928-1929 (Box 8)
        (Pan-Pacific Union)
      - Ford, Henry, 1928 (Box 8)
        (Brazil clearing)
      - Ford Motor Co., 1928; 1937 (Box 8)
        (rubber; lumbang oil)
      - Ford-Robertson, F.C., 1956 (Box 8)
      - Foreign Missions-Methodist Board, 1946 (Box 8)
        (cooperation in botanical studies;)
      - Foreign Missions-Presbyterian, 1946 (Box 8)
      - Fosberg, F. Raymond, 1938-1958 (Box 8)
      - Foscue, Edwin J., 1951 (Box 8)
        (Lower Rio Grande Valley)
      - Foster, Adriance S., 1944-45, 1954 (Box 8)
        (Trochodendron, Comm. on Nat. Herb.)
      - Foucher, Laure Claire, 1928 (Box 8)
        (Batak, 1 letter to L.C.F.)
      - Fowler, James A., 1958 (Box 8)
        ("Science & Education")
      - Fox, Robert B., 1947-1949 (Box 8)
        (ethnobotany, Philippines)
      - Frake, Charles O., 1956 (Box 8)
      - France, Bethel, 1936 (Box 8)
      - Franceschi, F., 1910 (Box 8)
        (collecting-Rhus)
      - Francois, Tony, 1956 (Box 8)
      - Frank, Henry S., Pres. Lingnan Univ., 1947 (Box 8)
        (cooperation in botanical studies; China)
      - Frazao, C., 1947 (Box 8)
        ("Flora Fluminensis")
      - Freeman, J.W., 1938 (Box 8)
        (Java steel)
      - French, Franklin C., 1945 (Box 8)
      - Fried, Morton H., 1956 (Box 8)
      - Friend, Edwin W., 1909-1911 (Box 8)
      - Fries, Charles C., 1934 (Box 8)
        (report writing)
      - Friesner, Ray C., 1930-1946 (Box 8)
      - Frisbie, Robert D., 1947 (Box 8)
      - Frith, A.C., 1955 (Box 8)
        (British Honduras)
      - Frohne, Gertrude G., 1954-1957 (Box 8)
        (Alaska, Philippines)
      - Frost, Leon W., 1955 (Box 8)
        (aroids)
      - Fruwirth, C., 1921 (Box 8)
        (Vienna)
      - Fulford, Margaret, 1944 (Box 8)
        (A.F. collecting; also A.G.B.)
      - Fuller, George D., 1932-1938 (Box 8)
        (publication; roses)
      - Fuller, George N., 1932-1934 (Box 8)
        ("Encyclopedia of Michigan" biographies)
      - Fulmer, H.L., 1921; 1932 (Box 8)
      - Furey, Sherm Jr., 1933 (Box 8)
        (personal-Idaho)
      - Furstenberg, Albert C., 1938; 1947 (Box 8)
        (administration)